Class of 1954 Records, 1950-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1954 Records
1950-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1954.
RG 80
7 boxes (2.1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1954.
Historical Note
The Class of 1954 was the seventy-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1954 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1954, including materials from commencement, reunions, dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, extensive correspondences, questionnaires, financial information, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1954 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant" 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant" 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant" 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 4)
- Commencement-Dramatics, Photographs 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 5)
- Commencement-Music 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 6)
- Commencement-Photographs 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 7)
- Commencement-Speaker 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 8)
- Correspondence 1977-1980, n.d. (Box 2193, Folder 9)
- Correspondence 1981-1985 (Box 2193, Folder 10)
- Correspondence 1986-1988 (Box 2193, Folder 11)
- Correspondence 1989-1994 (Box 2193, Folder 12)
- Deferred Gifts and Bequests 1975-1984 (Box 2193, Folder 13)
- Freshman Handbook 1950-1951 (Box 2193, Folder 14)
- Freshman Reception 1950 (Box 2193, Folder 15)
- Class Fund Agent 1965-1984 (Box 2193, Folder 16)
- Groups 1950-1954, 1978 (Box 2194, Folder 1)
- History 1950 (Box 2194, Folder 2)
- Hoop Rolling 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 3)
- Ivy Day 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 4)
- Class Letters 1958-2002 (Box 2194, Folder 5)
- Class Officers 1954-1994 (Box 2194, Folder 6)
- Class Officers-Photographs 1950-1954 (Box 2194, Folder 7)
- Organization 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 8)
  See also Class of 1949 Organization
- Class President 1962-1984 (Box 2194, Folder 9)
- Questionnaires 1964, 1969, 1974 (Box 2194, Folder 10)
- Questionnaires 1970-1977 (Box 2194, Folder 11)
- Nominating Committee 1964-1979 (Box 2194, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2194, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 2194, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2194, Folder 15)
- Songs 1964, n.d. (Box 2194, Folder 16)
- Special Gifts Committee 1977-1988 (Box 2194, Folder 17)
- Treasurer 1959-1980 (Box 2194, Folder 18)
- Who's Who 1950 (Box 2194, Folder 19)
- Year Book 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 2195, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 2195, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 2195, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2195, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1974-1984 (Box 2195, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2195, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2195, Folder 7)
- 50th Reunion Book (Box OV)